{
    "subject": "Rex_Balsom",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Adriana_Cramer",
    "human_readable": "Rex Balsom is married to Adriana Cramer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9350289106369019,
            "question": "To whom is Rex Balsom married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9320027232170105,
            "question": "Is Rex Balsom married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182361364364624,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Rex Balsom and Adriana Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8915074467658997,
            "question": "Name a person who is married to Adriana Cramer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8701198697090149,
            "question": "Who is married to Adriana Cramer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8502146601676941,
            "question": "Is Adriana Cramer married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7187626957893372,
            "question": "Who is Rex Balsom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.713249921798706,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Rex Balsom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6367016434669495,
            "question": "What is the name of Adriana Cramer's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13030965626239777,
            "question": "Who are the spouses in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rex Balsom is married to Adriana Cramer.",
            "html": "yago_12607_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Adriana Cramer's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_12607_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Rex Balsom?",
            "html": "yago_12607_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Rex Balsom?",
            "html": "yago_12607_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12607_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can provide the following response:\n\n{'output': 'no'}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Rex Balsom and Adriana Cramer are mentioned together in several documents, there is no clear indication that they are married. In fact, one document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_12607/re-ranker-msmarco/86.txt) mentions Adriana Cramer as a significant romantic relationship for Rex Balsom, but it also mentions that they were divorced in 2008."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information supporting that Rex Balsom is married to Adriana Cramer. The texts mention their romantic relationship and interactions, but there is no indication of a marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Adriana Cramer and Rex Balsom were married but later got divorced.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Adriana Cramer is divorced from Rex Balsom.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Adriana Cramer was initially involved with Rex Balsom, but they eventually got married to other people; Rex married Gigi Morasco, and there is no information that suggests Rex is married to Adriana Cramer.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context explicitly states that Rex Balsom divorced Adriana Cramer in 2008, indicating they were not married at the time of the given information.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}